JONGHYUN KANG

1431 12th St. Fort Lee, NJ 07024

Phone: 201-916-0325 | Email: misterjaykay@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jonghyunkang/ GitHub: https://github.com/misterjaykay

Portfolio: https://misterjaykay.github.io/responsive-portfolio/

SUMMARY

Front-end web developer who can meet the deadline even in a pressured environment. Good at familiarizing myself in a new environment and in new projects. Will be earning a certificate in Full-stack development from Rutgers University, with developed skills in HTML, JavaScript, CSS, React.js, MySQL, express.js, and Node.js. Experience on a single webpage that helps users to browse financial information including stock markets and currency rates. An eager individual who is excited to challenge myself where I can utilize my skills to the max potential.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, jQuery, Sequelize, ORM, MySQL, express, React.js, MongoDB, PWA, NoSQL

PROJECTS

Project Name: Stock Watch

Link to GitHub: https://github.com/misterjaykay/Project-1

Link to Deployed Project: https://misterjaykay.github.io/Project-1/

- We wanted to create a Web Application where beginning investors can search and compare stock prices in a clear and concise environment. We wanted to enhance the user experience by adding sections for top stocks and a currency exchange table.
- My responsibilities in project was to create the front end page using HTML and CSS framework called Bulma and also help the team with the JavaScript code for Moment.js (for live time) and API calls.
- HTML, CSS including Bulma and Animate.css, JavaScript including Moment.js and JSON, and jQuery.

Project Name: Local Grub

Link to GitHub: https://github.com/eplatvoet/localgrub Link to Deployed Project: https://localgrub.herokuapp.com/

- Local Grub is an app that utilizes the Zomato & MapQuest API to gather local restaurant information based off of the user's city choice. This app was created to help promote small business throughout local communities, and give users that chance to explore restaurants besides the big chain/franchises.
- My responsibilities in project was to create back-end side of an app, that acquire user requested data using axios and send it to front-end side using express.js and also storing users saved restaurant data into MySQL database. Also using third-party API, render out the static map with pinned restaurant locations to front-end side.
- JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, jQuery, and JSON.

EXPERIENCE

4Raffine Inc, NORTHVALE, NJ JUN 2016 – JUL2020

Senior Sales Representative

- Manage all clients in North America; United States and Canada, accounting for 80% of monthly sales.
- Average of 8 new clients quarterly, adding \$15,000 to monthly revenue stream.
- Identify potential clients through targeted prospecting, cold calling and networking.
- In charge of launching new products by working closely with Design team, while analyzing client's specific demands and needs.
- In charge of assembling and managing IFJAG & ASD trade shows in major cities.
- Manage and organize inventory stock of over five thousand variety of goods in the company warehouse.
- Meet weekly with the company president to develop strategies and improve progress.

Shopping Holic TENAFLY, NJ MAR 2014 – APR 2016

Assistant Manager

- In charge new product development by working closely with Purchase team and Distribution team; based on client's needs.
- Responsible for inventory and quality check of over 500 goods in the company warehouse.
- In charge of online customer service; domestic and international customers.

LAVA Accessories CLOSTER, NJ JAN 2013 – MAR 2014

Sales Representative

- In charge of sales in New York, New Jersey, Connecticut, Georgia and Texas area.
- Responsible for organizing trade shows in Las Vegas, New York City, Georgia, and other major cities.
- In charge of identifying potential clients through cold calls and networking.
- Develop and maintain client relationships by contacting the clients in regular bases.

Home and Home RIDGEFIELD, NJ JAN 2010 – NOV 2012

Assistant Manager

- Manage the sales in Electronics and Appliances department; Refrigerator, Washer, Dryer, Television, etc.
- Responsible for stock management in general goods, electronics, and appliance.

 Operate appliances and electronics deliveries to customers including basic installation.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate: Rutgers University, New Brunswick, NJ A 12-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.